import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

Color primaryBlack = Color(0xff202c3b);

class DataSource2 {

  static List questionAnswers = [
    {
      "question": "Espresso",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 15 kj/4 kkal\nLemak = 0,32g\nLemak Jenuh = 0,163g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,163g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0g\nKolesterol = 0mg\nProtein = 0,21g\nKarbohidrat = 0g\nSerat = 0g\nGula = 0g\nSodium = 25mg\nKalium = 204mg\nKafein = 212mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Latt√©",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 282 kj/67 kkal\nLemak = 2,75g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,661g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,2g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0,699g\nKolesterol = 10mg\nProtein = 4,41g\nKarbohidrat = 6,18g\nSerat = 0g\nGula = 6,77g\nSodium = 63mg\nKalium = 277mg\nKafein = 175mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cold Brew",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 21 kj/5 kkal\nLemak = 0,00g\nProtein = 0,00g\nKarbohidrat = 0,00g\nSodium = 15mg\nKafein = 62mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Americano",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 63 kj/15 kkal\nLemak = 0,32g\nProtein = 0,00g\nKarbohidrat = 0,00g\nGula = 0,00g\nKafein = 225mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "White Coffee",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 544 kj/130 kkal\nLemak = 2,00g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,500g\nLemak Trans = 0,000g\nKolesterol = 10mg\nProtein = 4,00g\nKarbohidrat = 23,00g\nGula = 21,00g\nSodium = 65mg\nKalium = 15mg\nKafein = 173mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Arabica Coffee",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 1925 kj/460 kkal\nLemak = 19,00g\nKolesterol = 55mg\nProtein = 7,00g\nKarbohidrat = 67,00g\nSerat = 2,0g\nGula = 55,00g\nSodium = 240mg\nKafein = 125mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kopi Tubruk",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 15 kj/4 kkal\nLemak = 0,32g\nLemak Jenuh = 0,003g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,003g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0g\nKolesterol = 0mg\nProtein = 0,2g\nKarbohidrat = 0,68g\nSerat = 0g\nGula = 0g\nSodium = 4mg\nKalium = 57mg\nKafein = 185mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Cappucino",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 233 kj/56 kkal\nLemak = 2,99g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,704g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,18g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0,756g\nKolesterol = 9mg\nProtein = 3,06g\nKarbohidrat = 4,36g\nSerat = 0,2g\nGula = 4,81g\nSodium = 38mg\nKalium = 175mg\nKafein = 160mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kopi Luwak",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 460 kj/110 kkal\nLemak = 2,00g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,500g\nLemak tak Jenuh Trans = 0,000g\nKolesterol = 0mg\nProtein = 4,00g\nKarbohidrat = 18,00g\nSerat = 3,0g\nGula = 21,00g\nSodium = 95mg\nKafein = 200mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Affogato",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 110 kj/26 kkal\nLemak = 1,47g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,343g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,004g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0,041g\nKolesterol = 0mg\nProtein = 0,39g\nKarbohidrat = 2,91g\nSerat = 0g\nGula = 2,26g\nSodium = 12mg\nKalium = 89mg\nKafein = 77mg"
    },
    {
      "question": "Machiato",
      "answer":
          "Ukuran porsi = 1 cangkir                                                      \nPer porsi\nEnergi = 110 kj/26 kkal\nLemak = 1,47g\nLemak Jenuh = 1,343g\nLemak tak Jenuh Ganda = 0,004g\nLemak tak Jenuh Tunggal = 0,041g\nKolesterol = 0mg\nProtein = 0,39g\nKarbohidrat = 2,91g\nSerat = 0g\nGula = 2,26g\nSodium = 12mg\nKalium = 89mg\nKafein = 85mg"
    },
  ];
}
